const quizData = `[
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "The average woman is 5 inches / 13 centimeters shorter than the average man.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Science: Mathematics",
      "question": "An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Music",
      "question": "Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "question": "The game 'Battlefield 1' takes place during World War I.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Vehicles",
      "question": "The majority of Subaru vehicles are made in China.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Board Games",
      "question": "The Angry Video Game Nerd's alter ego is 'Board James'",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Entertainment: Film",
      "question": "Sean Connery wasn't in 'Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull' because he found retirement too enjoyable.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "category": "Science: Mathematics",
      "question": "A Millinillion is a real number.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]`;


    export {quizData}